{
    "subject": "resource/2009\u201310_Manchester_City_F.C._season",
    "predicate": "property/team",
    "object": "resource/Crystal_Palace_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "The team for the 2009\u201310 Manchester City F.C. season was Crystal Palace F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9803072810173035,
            "question": "Which team was Crystal Palace F.C. playing against during the 2009-10 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9657034277915955,
            "question": "What team faced Manchester City F.C. in the 2009-10 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9614483714103699,
            "question": "Manchester City faced which team in the 2009-10 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9555525779724121,
            "question": "What football club was Crystal Palace F.C.'s opponent during the 2009\u201310 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9541457295417786,
            "question": "Name the team that played against Manchester City in the 2009-10 season."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169819951057434,
            "question": "Who was the opposing team to Manchester City F.C. in the 2009-10 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9101512432098389,
            "question": "Against which team did Manchester City compete during the 2009\u201310 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9048951864242554,
            "question": "What season did Manchester City F.C. play against Crystal Palace F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8951647877693176,
            "question": "Who played against Manchester City F.C. during the 2009\u201310 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8812752366065979,
            "question": "In what year did Manchester City F.C. play against Crystal Palace F.C.?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The team for the 2009\u201310 Manchester City F.C. season was Crystal Palace F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8595_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who played against Manchester City F.C. during the 2009\u201310 season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8595_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What season did Manchester City F.C. play against Crystal Palace F.C.?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8595_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Against which team did Manchester City compete during the 2009\u201310 season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8595_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8595_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not contain any information that supports the statement \"The team for the 2009\u201310 Manchester City F.C. season was Crystal Palace F.C.\" Instead, the provided context talks about events related to a match between Manchester City and Crystal Palace in a more recent time frame, focusing on the 2023/24 season or earlier."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}